Why?
The killer.
You're awake. How are you feeling?
I'm fine.
I feel much better.
Why was it so serious this time?
Maybe I overused my powers,
and on top of that,
I forced a time reversal.
I'm sorry. It's all because of me.
It's not your fault.
Fortunately, you stopped me in time.
Otherwise,
I would have committed an unforgivable crime.
Crime?
If I kill a living person,
I will turn into an evil spirit
and then be annihilated.
I won't abuse your powers anymore.
It's no big deal.
I just need some rest.
Xingcan,
I have one more request.
Tell me.
I don't want you to risk your life
to investigate anymore.
That person is too dangerous.
I don't want you to be in danger again.
I promise you.
There's one more thing I'm thinking about.
If a hard drive could bring down the Ling family,
why didn't your father tell me directly
when he saw me?
You... you mean...
So this matter
is not as simple as it seems.
Can you contact my father now?
No.
True.
My father might have already been reincarnated.
I hope his new life is happy and fulfilling.
This time,
we need to follow the past timeline
and gradually advance the investigation.
We need to gather more witnesses and physical evidence.
Okay, I'll follow your lead.
You... you seem
to have changed.
Really?
For the better or for the worse?
Probably for the better.
Why aren't they here yet? It's almost time.
I'm ready.
What are you doing?
I might not be able to hold out this time
for as long as before.
You need to be extra careful.
We agreed.
You can't abuse your power anymore.
Then how are you going to get in?
I'll secretly check the password later
and go in when no one is around.
Wouldn't that waste another day for nothing?
I can do it.
Using my power once
won't be a problem.
No.
You're already so weak.
I'm not weak.
It's your fault for wasting an opportunity.
What do we do now?
What else can we do?
Just wait for another chance.
Wait.
Look.
If I had known things would turn out like this,
you wouldn't have had to do that last time.
The equipment is working fine.
Now we just wait for her to show up.
Are you sure you still want to keep looking for her?
She saved you in the last timeline.
Judging from this,
she is not inherently bad.
Although she backstabbed me before.
However,
I want to talk to her one more time.
Mucheng.
Xingcan.
I was just looking for you.
I have something to tell you.
Let's talk in the car.
And this is?
He's with me.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
How much money do you want?
I must win this lawsuit.
You can't win this lawsuit.
He has already forged evidence of you blackmailing him.
What did you say?
Work with me.
I guarantee you will regain your freedom.
Why should I believe you?
Because of this surveillance footage.
Who are you?
I'm dropping the lawsuit against the company.
I admit
I was immature before,
and shouldn't have caused trouble for the company.
But I know
that everything I have was given by you.
So please be generous,
give me another chance,
and I will definitely behave.
Mucheng.
Thank you.
Hearing what you said,
I am truly relieved.
Mucheng,
on behalf of the company,
I apologize to you.
Mr. Ling,
what do you mean?
I can't hear what they're saying.
Mucheng,
I will return the contract to you as soon as possible,
and have the company allocate a sum of money to you.
Really.
I promised you.
But about this,
you must not tell anyone.
I took a big risk for this.
I understand.
The company is full of my father's people now.
So you have to trust me.
Who you met during this time,
and what you said,
you must tell me.
Okay.
Right now, the company is full of my father's people.
So you must believe me.
Who you've met during this time,
what you've said,
you must tell me.
How come this guy seems like a different person?
What else did he tell you?
You didn't tell him about us, did you?
Of course I didn't.
But isn't he just confessing without being pressed?
At a time like this,
he pushed everything onto Ling Hengsheng.
Maybe I'm overthinking it.
I thought about it carefully.
For so many years,
he has been quite good to me.
Lawyer Gu,
if there's nothing else,
I'll get going.
Contact us anytime if you have any problems.
Bye.
Why do I always feel something is wrong?
More than that.
Ling Ze is suddenly so nice to Mu Cheng.
It makes it hard to guess his next move.
I'm afraid he's hiding evil intentions this time.
You are not from this era.
Why do you ask that all of a sudden?
We've been together for so long.
Your words and actions, every move you make,
are so strange,
like an ancient person.
I...
Tell me.
I won't tell anyone else.
Come on, tell me.
I've just been wandering in this world for a thousand years.
So you are an immortal?
Of course not.
I'm just a lonely soul
who cannot enter the cycle of reincarnation.
Why can't you enter the cycle of reincarnation?
I
am waiting for someone.
Who?
It must be a woman, right?
I knew it.
Yes.
I couldn't tell.
You are an affectionate lonely soul.
Is she pretty?
Is she your wife?
Also a ghost?
You have so many questions.
Stingy.
What's wrong?
That guy
asked me out.
Asking to meet at home this late,
he definitely has bad intentions.
It's fine. You're here anyway.
Mr. Gu, you're here.
And this is?
He is my assistant.
He just started today.
It's fine. Please come in.
Mr. Ling,
You called us over so late.
Is there something wrong?
Mr. Gu,
I have something very important to tell you.
What important matter?
Just tell me directly.
Please wait a moment.
I know you're that reporter's daughter.